<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Tellers.]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Tellers.]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/tellers/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 19:16:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/tellers/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 19:16:07 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Storytelling for dummies]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Storytelling for dummies</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/02873330-cfd6-4e21-be49-d0cf1f821e27.jpg">,<p>You work in marketing and you have heard about the powerful impact of storytelling on your business growth. You watched a couple of videos and downloaded an e-book on building stories for brands. It seems to be so easy to implement this strategy in your content creation. And still, something is missing, something is not working out.</p>,<p>You know that there are various ways to tell a story. You also know about the Hero's journey structure. What if I tell you there are <a href="https://blog.bufferapp.com/storytelling-formulas" title="">many more</a>? </p>,<p>Learning the notions, watching tutorials and scrolling through the infographics won't help you figure out the basic strategy for your business unless you understand the who-is-who on the storytelling.</p>,<p>Who is the hero of your legend? Is it the company that solves the world problems and creates the brighter future? Is it you, the people behind it? Is it your product?<br>The true hero of your story must be the client, the reader.</p>,<p>Storytelling has an aim to impact people through a compelling tale, that would provoke emotions and build the connection. Like in all kinds of marketing, the goal of storytelling is to influence and inform. The difference between the pure "selling" and creating stories around the brand is in the value that storytelling gives to the readers and the way it resonates with them.</p>,<p>How can you use it in your content creation strategy, concretely?<br>For example, you can follow these steps:</p>,<p>- Show the world they are living in now, the struggle they have;</p>,<p>- Then move to the opportunity to have a painless life, a future where the problem is elegantly solved;</p>,<p>- Show the transformation they will go through and how it will change them;</p>,<p>- Go back to the now and point out what is not working with the current situation;</p>,<p>- Move back to the bright future and introduce your solution.</p>,<p>You can play with the techniques and invent your own ones. It can be used while creating content like articles and videos, as well as in your sales pitch and even head hunting process.</p>,<p>Creating compelling stories that are remarkable and memorable is hard but it's worth the effort. The emotional bond that they set between your brand and the users is the strongest advantage you can have on the market.</p>,<p>Build your strategy basing on this main point and you will figure out the way it works best for you.</p>,<p>Image by Patrick Tomasso via Unsplash.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/tellers/storytelling-for-dummies/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5a2cddf0-4f79-483c-89bd-26267ad5a620</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 18:32:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growth hacking for startups]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/2c21150c-9cd7-4699-a9e8-caa4fb652128.jpg">,<h1><strong>Growth hacking for startups</strong></h1>,<p>Marketing is evolving at the speed of light: no longer we only print flyers and post product pictures on Facebook.</p>,<p>In order to catch consumers’ attention and sell our technology, we need to apply some <strong>growth hacking</strong>. Behind these loud words stands “the process of rapid experimentation across marketing channels and product development to identify the most effective, <strong>efficient ways to grow a business</strong>”.</p>,<p>Where is such a fast growth requested on the daily basis? That’s right, <strong>startups</strong> is the right place to learn about this new vision on customer acquisition.</p>,<p>What are the tricks that startupers implement and see the (almost) immediate results?</p>,<h3><strong>HACK THEM</strong></h3>,<ul><li>Define your <strong>voice</strong>, even if you are a B2B business - see the example of <a href="https://twitter.com/powwownow?lang=en" title="">Powpownow</a>.</li><li><strong>Be bold</strong> - remember what <a href="https://growthhackers.com/growth-studies/airbnb" title="">Airbnb did with Craigslist</a>? You can also set an Adwords campaign with your competitors’ keywords, mentioning that you are "alternative to" or "better than" them.</li><li>Send <strong>goodies</strong> - bombard the prospects with fun or useful stuff in their mailbox. Send them postcards, offer samples of branded tea. Have fun!</li><li>Learn about <strong>guerrilla marketing</strong> and principles of <strong>word-of-mouth</strong> - these are the cheapest way to attract your prospects’ attention.</li><li>Provide <strong>exceptional customer service</strong>. This must be the strongest point of your business.</li><li>Sign up for <strong>Hubspot’s Marketing and Sales newsletter</strong> for a daily boost of inspiration, read Growth Hackers’ articles, follow marketing gurus like <strong>Seth Godin</strong>, <strong>Larry Kim, Shane Show </strong>and<strong> Neil Patel</strong>.</li></ul>,<h3><strong>GO SOCIAL</strong></h3>,<ul><li>On social media be open, friendly, keep up to your strategy and voice, answer all messages and comments.</li><li>Write <strong>themed content</strong> and tag the relevant people and companies on Twitter with the link to the article.</li><li><strong>Twitter</strong> - use <a href="https://tweepi.com/ " title="">Tweepi</a> to monitor followers and <a href="http:// https//tweetdeck.twitter.com/" title="">Tweetdeck</a> for the fresh content based on your keywords. Make a <a href="https://hashtagify.me/" title="">research</a> on hashtags and stick to them.</li><li><strong>Instagram</strong> - always use hashtags, find relevant people and profiles and follow them, as well as their followers, comment on their pictures, be authentic in your comments and never use automated likes and responses.</li><li><strong>Facebook</strong> - tag relevant people and companies when sharing new content, post in thematic groups, use smart advertising setting up the needed demographic and preferences.</li><li><strong>LinkedIn</strong> - upload presentations, leaflets and visuals on SlideShare, post on Pulse, connect to stars in your industry, post in professional groups.</li><li>Use automation for posting​ (<strong><a href="http://linkhumans.com/blog/buffer-vs-hootsuite" title="">Buffer or Hootsuite</a></strong>), find optimal time and post frequently.</li><li>Make your own visuals: use <strong><a href="http:// canva.com/" title="">Canva</a></strong>, <strong><a href="http://pixlr.com/" title="">Pixlr</a></strong> and <strong><a href="https://spark.adobe.com/" title="">Spark</a></strong> for fast and simple online design, free photo banks like <strong><a href="http://unsplash.com/" title="">Unsplash</a></strong>.</li></ul>,<h3><strong>MONITOR!</strong></h3>,<ul><li><strong>Almost all your actions online and offline must direct prospects on your website.</strong></li><li>Always <strong>test and measure the results </strong>of your marketing campaigns. Growth hacking without analytics is like throwing pasta against the wall over and over again wondering which one is going to stick. If you test and measure it, though, you may see that the best-sticking pasta is fettuccine alla Bolognese.</li><li>Use Google Analytics, KPIs on your social networks and automation tools. Search for new tools that would be relevant for your business.</li></ul>,<h3><strong>KEEP GOING</strong></h3>,<p>The impact of growth hacking is hard to measure in precise numbers because of the complexity of all the <strong>moves</strong> and <strong>tricks</strong> marketers use. We create the buzz, the talk around our businesses, glueing our logos into people's subconscious.</p>,<p>Being a growth hacker in a startup won't give you physical palpable results as often as you wish. But the warm feeling of satisfaction when a prospect exclaims <strong>"Yes, I heard about you, folks!"</strong> is definitely worth it.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/tellers/growth-hacking-for-startups/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e6110863-ff21-4c0d-8465-ff53bacf3b5c</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 15:59:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to survive a burnout?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ce968d60-a661-4ad8-9c01-da564ca768b8.jpg">,<h1><strong>How to survive a burnout?</strong></h1>,<p>You are a hard worker. Probably, even a workaholic. You can come back home from the office, open your laptop, sit and understand in half an hour that you are still wearing your coat. And only because your partner says you are.</p>,<p>You feel tired every day, sometimes you feel less accomplished as usual, and you may feel powerless. But at some point you see it differently: apathy, simple tasks are suddenly unbearable, even the activities you enjoyed are now dull and stressful. It is not better after a day off which brings you to a conclusion: you’ve been burned out.</p>,<p><strong>First of all</strong>, you should underline in your agenda that coming back to normal will take some time. It has been something bothering you for long to cause a burnout. </p>,<p><strong>Second</strong>, be with your family, friends, your dog or your gym mates. People who understand your feelings and surround you with their support are the best cure of all times.</p>,<p><strong>Third</strong>, reschedule your activities. Add more walking in the park, put less working hours, less cigarettes and sitting in the office. It may cause you some delays, so plan carefully. And remember: if you continue pushing yourself towards the deadline it won’t do, it will be just worse, so you DESERVE the rest, do not feel guilty for your soul sickness.</p>,<p><strong>Fourth</strong>, put the imaginary wall between you and outter world negativity. Should it be explained?</p>,<p><strong>Fifth</strong>, laugh, sing, dance, do what makes you feel stupid or funny. It does not matter, nobody is watching, and this will definitely burst your mood and creativity.</p>,<p><strong>Sixth</strong>, eat colorful food, which is mostly fruit and vegetables, and not jelly beans and Skittles.</p>,<p>Vitamins are essential for you not only now when you need to recover, so put is in your to-eat list daily.</p>,<p><strong>Seventh</strong>, listen to music. My own tip is to lie down on the couch or bed, close your eyes and play your favorite music through the headphones. Ten minutes and you are efficient again. Also, consider listening to Mozart’s music: it’s therapeutical effect was proved by many scientists.</p>,<p>And <strong>eight</strong>, rethink all your working activity. You just understood that this rhythm was bad for you. So, you are planning to change it and dedicate more time to your health. </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/tellers/how-to-survive-a-burnout/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3e55a414-3ec2-40ce-884b-b3f98e0f5251</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 17:29:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blugle]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fplayer.vimeo.com%2Fvideo%2F210774511&url=https%3A%2F%2Fvimeo.com%2F210774511&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.vimeocdn.com%2Fvideo%2F626671805_1280.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=vimeo" width="1000" height="429" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<p>Produced for <a href="http://www.blugle.tv/" title="">Blugle</a>.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/tellers/blugle/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8f35641a-eaf3-4cb0-8221-b0078758f6ad</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 18:10:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[7 magical traits of Brussels]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2Fmhsc_6O7iUc%3Fstart%3D2%26feature%3Doembed%26start%3D2&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3Dmhsc_6O7iUc&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2Fmhsc_6O7iUc%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mhsc_6O7iUc&amp;t=2s</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ea4084d1-c474-4051-9d3b-9d2e77c77722</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 18:11:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[If you move to Moscow]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FeXrzXT2vJ8g%3Fstart%3D3%26feature%3Doembed%26start%3D3&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DeXrzXT2vJ8g&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FeXrzXT2vJ8g%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eXrzXT2vJ8g&amp;t=3s</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9a68e714-6e6c-462a-b7b3-6cc61f0de128</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 18:10:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Barcelona Dream]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FJ8dtdqVwbfE%3Fstart%3D4%26feature%3Doembed%26start%3D4&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DJ8dtdqVwbfE&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FJ8dtdqVwbfE%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/tellers/barcelona-dream/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7eecc121-a1ed-4450-80b4-5e4a0165c1fb</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 18:08:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We tell stories that make your customers fall in love with you, just like people fall in love with puppies.</p>,<p>Do you want to seduce, engage, educate, benefit your client? </p>,<p>Do you want to grow a successful business focused on a great and only great customer experience?</p>,<p>With a distinctive expertise in creative fields, growth hacking and storytelling, Tellers will provide you with the best service to raise awareness about your brand, engage customers and delight existing clients.</p>,<p>We are a company with strong work ethics: we meet deadlines in advance, answer each email and prepare beautiful power points. </p>,<p>Talk to us in 🇬🇧  🇮🇹  🇷🇺  🇫🇷  🇺🇦</p>,<p><strong>Our clients:</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e20d5c65-258b-4a18-902d-9af0d3e9ae9d.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/tellers/tellers-develop-storytelling-for-businesses/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">844f442e-aacb-422b-8ab7-ab0d2b4b9d53</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 10:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>